FERNANDO ALFARO

Download PDF

Fernandogalfaro@lewisu.edu (224) - 431-3506

Profile

STUDENT

Constantly learning, evolving, and pursuing new skills to help the computer science field advance

Summary

of Qualifications Training

Trained new employees fufill high risk financial jobs.

Customer Service

Over 4 years of experince assisting customers, problem-solving, and resolving escalated issues Research

Efficient in learning, analyzing, and acuring data from hard to learn environments

Technical

HTML. Python MS Excel CSS MS Word MacOS MS Powerpoint Windows 10/11 Javascript

Experience

Designer Shoe Warehouse

Main Cashier

2015-2016

Process over 50+ cash/card purchases, managed cash drawer, and solve customer problems.

BMO Harris Bank

2017-2019 Teller

Managed and handled cash drawer. Processed deposits, withdraws, and payments. Sold mortgages, credit cards, and HELOC's.

Abri Credit Union

2019-2020

Universal Banker

 $Handlded\ account\ opening, loan\ applications, and\ fraud\ disputues.\ Handled\ account\ transactions;$ deposits, withdraws, cashiers checks, and payments. Networked with clients to build raport and dicuss account reports.

Education

Joliet Junior College - Joliet, Illinois Associates in Applied Science, Computer Science -3.6 GPA

Lewis University - Romeoville, Illinois Bachelors in Science, Computer Science -3.9 GPA EXP: August 2024